(There was a man)
(That sailed the seas)
What are you looking at?
How come...
Right, the GPS locator.
Angie, have you considered
why we found each other again in this life?
Maybe...Heaven wanted to give us
another chance?
I think Chow Kai-hin and Koo Ning-yuk
couldn't part with each other.
They installed a GPS locator
so they could find each other in this life.
It may be another mistake
to find each other.
I made a mistake.
I let you down.
I also let Chow Kai-hin down.
I wasted his effort to find Koo Ning-yuk.
Actually I'm not as good as Koo Ning-yuk.
Angie...you're fine.
You're great!
Even when I asked for a divorce,
you didn't blame me.
You said Heaven wanted to give us
a second chance.
I think Chow Kai-hin fought for this chance.
He taught me how to love someone
and the meaning of till death do us part.
Man Nga-kei, will you marry me again?
I promise I will settle down.
I will always be there for you.
I will only love you.
OK!
(He's coming home)
(Don't you cry)
You and Angie want to get married again?
After we have been through so much,
I realized Angie would do anything for me.
It was my fault I didn't cherish her.
Now I won't let her go again.
You treated her so bad.
Would she agree to it?
Angie and I talked about it.
We'll move to Fukuoka.
It's very nice and a lot of Hongkongers
have moved there.
Pack up and go? That's like child's play!
You abandon everything here for no reason
and start over somewhere so far away?
Are you two sure?
You decided for me without even asking me.
What makes you think I'll like it?
I'm not eating!
Just think...she used deepfake,
and harassed Yau You-fong and Man Nga-kei.
One person alone can't do all that.
Who else could be involved?
That'll depend on who benefits the most
from Siu Zi-yiu's death.
We recovered Siu Zi-yiu's phone.
Thanks.
Dinner didn't go so well, right?
No, it's about the same as usual.
Don't think too much about it.
Mom gave each of us an amulet.
Remember to hang onto it, OK?
Angie...
Let's reconsider moving overseas.
Didn't we already agree
to start over somewhere else?
I know you care about Mom.
She told us to think carefully just now.
She doesn't exactly object, right?
If she really doesn't want to go,
I won't force her.
But I really don't want to stay.
I have too many unhappy memories...
Mom is just saying it.
I know what she's thinking.
She was quite upset last time I moved out
when we got married.
I remember the time she fell down at home
it was the first time I wasn't
living with her.
She was in a foul mood
and couldn't sleep at night.
She was in a bit of a trance
and she was tired and weak.
I could feel she was lonely.
I feel bad about leaving her alone
in Hong Kong.
Let's decide later, OK?
OK, we'll do this later.
I asked you to come up
because I want you to see if
anything in here belongs to you.
If there are, take them back.
If not, I'll donate them
to earn some merit for my daughter.
Hello?
Get in.
Be careful!
Thanks, Sang.
Angie, go home and get some rest.
The director said we'll manage. Thanks.
Thank you.
Angie, how are you feeling?
Carrying the amulet from Mom
makes me feel unwell.
I felt something heavy on my chest.
Don't carry it if you don't feel well.
It's no big deal.
What is it, Angie?
I'm not sure if I'm being oversensitive.
I was going through the sketchbook
again last night,
I noticed the child bride
had a birth mark on her calf.
But Liz didn't have any birth marks.
Is it possible she was not the child bride?
I did my research.
She came from an opera troupe.
After she was sold to the Chow family,
she occasionally performed in
different outfits.
Murder suspect fell from
an industrial building,
broke her left leg
and died a horrible death.
Auntie Mui said Master Chow's dog
broke its left leg.
Mom was the child bride?
These amulets are not the same.
Why would Angie's amulet say these things?
I'm glad you're home.
Why are you sprawled out on my bed again?
Mom?
Wow, you made such a mess.
Move over. Let me clean that up for you.
No...I'll do it myself.
Why did you give me earrings?
Remember it's been two months
since we started dating?
Mom is connected to Sylvia's death?!
Mom?
Oh, you're home early.
What? You just got back to work,
are you busy?
It's OK.
I'm about to do laundry,
but I don't have a full load.
Let me wash your jacket.
No need.
Why not? You've been wearing that
for a long time.
I really don't need to wash it.
Give it to me...
No need, Mom...
When did you find this?
Why was Mom's ring Sylvia's flat?
I found it behind the sofa earlier.
Is it very important?
Your Dad gave me this ring
when we got married.
Our wedding day is engraved on it.
Mom, I'm going on a business trip.
I need to go pack.
Will you eat dinner before you go?
Davis?
Angie, can I stay here for a few days?
Bad time? There's a guy in there?
Don't be silly. Come on in.
What is it? Had a fight with Mom?
Yeah, about moving overseas.
I plan to give her time to think it over.
Don't pressure her.
I know you're trying to persuade her
because of me.
Why don't we take a trip to Japan?
Maybe she'll change her mind.
I haven't been here since our divorce.
I thought you tossed my paintings.
Of course not. You did such a great job.
Let me get you something to eat.
Relax a bit. Take a shower.
You'll find the towels in the same place.
(several days later)
Son, you haven't answered me in a few days.
You won't tell me where you are.
You weren't like this before.
Oh, he's staying with Angie.
Angie!
Morning, Mom!
Morning!
Great! I called you up suddenly
and you're here in such a short time.
Davis dropped you off?
Yes, he's working on an urgent project.
He's in the office now.
He didn't tell me he's staying with you.
Sorry, Mom! I thought he did.
He lied about going on a business trip
and left me on read.
I don't know what he's up to.
Am I really so scary?
Of course not!
I think he wants to give you time to think.
We'd love to have you move to
Japan with us.
He's already thinking about
how to design the roof
so you can grow something there.
He really cares about you.
Come on, smile!
Mom, where are you going? I'll go with you.
We can do something to relax.
The restaurant downstairs is quite good.
Let's go there.
Why do you have that earring?
What about it?
Take it off, let me see...
Hold on...Mom, wait...
Take it off...
Yiu Wai-lan...
Crime Unit, New Territories East.
Ms. Yiu, we suspect you're connected to
Siu Zi-yiu's murder.
Please come down to the Police station.
Yiu Wai-lan, over the past month,
have you met with Siu Zi-yiu?
No.
We found a video from
Siu Zi-yiu's cloud storage
which was recorded two weeks ago.
It showed you visiting her studio
and you got into a fight with her.
You warned her to stop harassing
Yau You-fong
or you'll make sure nothing good
would come to her.
Why did you hide your meeting
with Siu Zi-yiu?
Is it because you think she tried to
con money from your son
and you killed her in a rage?
No!
You're back!
What a feast!
It's the third anniversary of
our first date.
Sorry, I didn't get you anything.
It's OK. I'm wearing the pearl earrings
you gave me before we got married.
Aren't they pretty?
It's not Sylvia's earring.
Why do you look so stunned?
Nothing.
Cheers!
Well? Is everything OK?
Mom has a birth mark on her calf.
What do you mean?
Since we told her we're getting married,
she's been acting weird.
I agree. She's been acting weird.
She contacted you?
What did she say?
Not much. What happened?
I'm confused...
I don't know how to explain.
Someone I thought was close to me,
someone I thought I knew so well...
I dare not think anymore.
I'm afraid I'll lose everyone.
Don't be silly. You still have me.
Sylvia...
Who?
What did I say?
You called me Sylvia!
You're still thinking about Sylvia!
No, Angie! I'm sorry!
I don't know why...
Because she had a place in your heart.
You missed her subconsciously.
Haven't we been through enough?
Why can't you make up your mind?
Angie, it's not like that...
I'm Man Nga-kei.
I'm the one you're marrying.
Why?
Haven't I done enough? Why? Tell me why!
I'm sorry...
I have been drinking...I'm not sober.
Maybe...because I gave the same
earring to Sylvia.
What did you say?
You gave the same earring to her?
What do you take me for?
Her replacement?
No, Angie! You're not...
How could you be so cruel?
It's not like that.
Why?
Yau You-fong, I hate you!
Calm down, Angie!
You've been lying from the start.
No, Angie! Please calm down.
It's not enough you hurt me once.
How many times must you hurt me? Tell me...
I hate you...
Calm down...
I hate you!
Is that Sylvia's head?
I'm asking you if that was Sylvia's head?
Did you kill Sylvia?
What kind of human being are you?
You killed her and put her head
inside a stuffed animal?
Have you gone mad?
Just think I kept saying
my beloved Angie is the most
gentle and simple.
She's not capable of killing anyone.
See? I sounded you out and
you gave yourself away.
Are you the killer?
You sounded me out?
You knew Sylvia all along.
But you never said anything.
What else are you holding out on me?
How could you be so heartless
to kill Sylvia?
Because she deserved it!
I paid her to help me
but she stole you from me.
Help you to do what?
I was heartbroken when you
asked for a divorce.
I saw that tramp on a fortune telling show.
She claimed she could help couples
patch things up.
So I approached her anonymously.
She said if I gave her our birth data,
she could help me
and I'll have good news in 60 days.
For a while, I kept running into you
and I thought she could really help me.
But she turned around and took you from me.
I tried everything I could
to dig up compromising materials
to discredit her.
I want revenge.
When I went up to her studio.
Guess what I saw?
She did nothing about our birth data.
She bound her birth data with yours
and tried to con money from you.
Luckily, you didn't fall for it.
But you still care a lot about her.
I know she had enemies...
I continued to discredit her
so you'll see her for who she is.
Then she showed up at my doorstep.
But she didn't come here to apologize.
She told me you'll never be mine.
If you're so confident,
let me call Davis now
and tell him everything you have done.
No...I beg you...
Get away from me...
Sorry, I didn't mean it...
Bloody hell!
You accused me of conning Davis?
It's not just money.
He'll give me anything.
While you, like these paintings you see,
are bored like a stiff.
Don't touch Davis' paintings...
Help...
Sylvia...
I don't con just anyone.
I like him because he's cute and fun.
I'm ignoring him for now
and then I'll spill the beans on you.
Angie?
Angie...
I didn't mean it...
It was self-defense.
You killed Sylvia?
She came up to confront me.
She said many things and tried to hurt me.
I grabbed a knife and stabbed her.
Now what?
Let's call the Police.
I won't go to jail.
I'll lose everything.
You should go...I'll take care of this.
How?
Angie, turn yourself in.
Sylvia came up looking for trouble.
It was self-defense, right?
I'm Davis' ex-wife, she was his ex.
The Police won't believe me.
Don't call the Police.
Liz, I beg you...please help me.
Don't say anything. I'm begging you.
It's OK. You should go.
I'll take care of it.
I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean to kill her.
But on second thought...she deserved it.
After I killed her,
I cut off her head
and removed her fingerprints.
Then I took her body to the hillside.
Even if the body was discovered,
It'll take some time to identify her.
That witch had so many enemies,
I'm not on top of the list.
How could you do something so inhumane?
Did you arrange for those weird things
that happened to me?
Yes. In the beginning,
I just didn't want anyone to know
I killed Sylvia...
Those born in the Year of the Dragon,
Snake and Horse,
your luck with romance is in the east.
You used my deepfake account
and posed as Sylvia to livestream.
Did you know you'll get me in trouble?
I'm sorry. I only did the livestreaming
so people would think she was still alive.
I didn't realize not using the app properly
would get in trouble.
What you did will lead the Police to
my doorstep
once they start to investigate.
Then don't let people get suspicious.
You're good with deepfake,
if you pose as Sylvia,
there won't be any flickering
and people won't suspect anything.
You want me to pose as her?
Please, Liz? Only you can help me.
In reverse...it means luck
is not on our side.
But that brat is still not convinced.
He planned to talk to her after work.
I hope he'll wake up.
Auntie, I'm sorry.
I'm due back at the TV station
for a meeting.
I'll drop by your place tonight
after work to drink it.
Since you won't let go,
I had to be more thorough.
Sylvia, open the door.
Let's sit down and talk, OK?
Sylvia...
(Scumbag, I don't want to see you anymore)
(I will not forgive you)
(I'm returning your things)
(What you owe me, I won't let it slide)
You promised me you'll quit when
he stops looking for Sylvia.
I will. You should go.
You hurt yourself and lied to me.
Because I realized when I'm hurt,
you'll care about me
and you'll stay with me.
I'll do anything for you.
I can sacrifice anything.
But you sacrificed Liz.
You killed someone and
she covered up for you.
You think she was sincere?
She felt guilty.
She didn't really want to help me.
We were inseparable since college.
But because of you...
She never liked you
and always criticized you.
I can put up with that...
But in the end, when we were
about to break up,
she went to bed with you!
I couldn't get in touch with
her afterwards.
Then she started livestreaming on her own.
If I wasn't worried about her
blowing our cover,
I wouldn't have tipped her off.
I really must go. Bye!
But I need to find her.
Finally, she called me back.
Hello, Liz?
I know I must settle this.
But I can't let you find me.
(No signal from device)
I finally went to see her.
Come with me. Turn yourself in.
Let go. I won't turn myself in.
I'm wanted by the Police.
You want me dead too?
You said you would leave.
I'm only helping you because
you're my bestie.
I'm your bestie?
You're helping me because you feel guilty.
You thought I didn't know?
You slept with Davis, didn't you?
Why did you do this to me?
How long have we known each other?
Yes...I slept with Davis.
But I was drunk, I acted on an impulse.
All along, I felt guilty towards you.
But what about him?
He proposed the very next day!
What was his reason?
Because he knew I'm the one he loves.
No!
He was a player. He felt guilty.
Let go of me!
Your marriage was a mistake.
Angie, turn yourself in.
I won't do it.
If Davis knew I killed someone,
he'd ditch me. Let go, Liz...
What about me?
I didn't kill anyone.
I'm innocent. Come with me.
Let go!
Man Nga-kei, where else can you go?
It was entirely my doing.
I'm letting go.
If I'm dead, then it'll be over.
Angie, calm down! Don't jump!
Angie...don't you remember?
We have been through so much since college.
Including this.
It'll be too late if you don't
turn yourself in.
I beg you...turn yourself in.
I slept with Davis.
All along, I felt guilty towards you.
I had to kill her. I had no choice.
She knew too much.
There's no other way.
(No signal from device)
(Chung Hung Industrial Building)
Angie?
No...Angie...
You and Liz cheated on me.
I can forgive you... because I love you.
I was thrilled when you proposed
the other day.
I thought you have changed.
But you suspected me
and tested me with that tramp's name!
I meant it when I proposed.
I genuinely wanted to be with you.
But you made me suspect my mother.
You said there was a problem with
the amulet Mom gave you.
But it wasn't the one she gave you.
I asked Uncle Kim about it.
What's the story with this peach wood sword
and Sylvia's earring?
I told Lan to put them in a flowerpot.
Lan told me the girl had your head spinning
and she was afraid you'd sell the flat.
So she confronted Sylvia at her studio
and secretly stole one of her earrings.
She gave it to me and asked me
to use magic to make that witch go away.
But we saw on the news
Sylvia died two weeks ago.
Which means when Lan came to me,
Sylvia was already dead.
If she killed Sylvia,
she wouldn't need me to chase her away.
When Lan found out Sylvia was murdered,
she felt very uneasy.
I told her to bury the peach wood sword
and the earring in a flowerpot
so the deceased can rest in peace
and reincarnate soon.
They said on the news,
they found next to Sylvia's body
a vajra, the Nine Grid and Eight Diagrams
and a Ghau prayer box.
Those are Buddhist apparatus.
Taoist like us don't use them.
Uncle Kim confirmed Mom didn't kill Sylvia.
But I don't know why you
switched the amulet.
So I hired a private detective
and found out you knew Sylvia all along
and I saw from your phone you asked
Sylvia to fix our Spouse Palace.
I also saw from your research,
you knew Chun Ming Mountain is deserted.
So you dumped Sylvia's body out there.
Yes...I did all that...
Now you know how far I would go for you.
How much I can sacrifice for you.
Angie, you killed someone.
You're not the Angie I know.
I did nothing wrong. They did.
Liz seduced you.
She betrayed me. She's not worthy.
She deserved to die.
Your mother wanted you for herself.
She wanted to be with you.
I want her to lose you forever.
Sylvia thinks she's so pretty
and she wanted you.
That's why I cut off her head
and put it here.
I want her to see how much
we love each other.
I want her to turn in her grave.
It wasn't entirely their fault.
What about me?
If I would settle down
and cherish you properly
you wouldn't turn out like this.
I just don't want to lose you.
I never expected things to
turn out like this.
This lot said
if we stick together and never give up,
we can overcome anything.
Why didn't that happen?
Angie...
Stay away...
I won't give up.
Please don't come any closer.
Turn yourself in.
We'll both plead your case.
Remember we agreed,
wherever the finishing line is,
I'll always be with you.
(Kwan Sir, Crime Unit)
How could I be so stupid?
Angie...
Stay away from me!
It's not what you think.
Shut up!
I don't want you to make any more mistakes.
The worst mistake I made was loving you
at all costs.
You're still lying to me at this moment.
Shut up...
Put down the knife...
You're lying to me...
Put it down, Angie!
No one can separate us anymore.
Drop the weapon...
No, let me go...
Man Nga-kei, you're suspected of committing
multiple murders and attempted murder.
You're now under arrest.
Yau You-fong...
Hey, son, you're awake!
You're looking good today.
If you suspected anything, you should have
called the Police sooner.
Don't wait till the last minute
to call Kwan Sir.
Do you realize how dangerous it was?
You almost died!
I can't believe Angie was more
terrifying than the witch.
All those weird things, the rashes
and the dead plants
were entirely her doing.
After Angie was arrested,
they came up to search for evidence.
Kwan Sir told me the vitamins
you were taking,
have been switched to penicillin.
Those rashes on your neck
were caused by penicillin.
Herbicide was added to the soil,
that's why the plants died.
Can't believe Angie did all that
behind our backs.
Mom...
I'm sorry!
I checked up on you.
It's over. Don't look back.
Just remember, only I want
what's best for you.
I hereby declare...
the defendant Man Nga-kei is found guilty of
murder and inflicting grievous bodily harm,
and is sentenced to life imprisonment.
Ning-yuk, I'll see you soon.
Wait for me.
(Chow Kai-hin & Ning-yuk)
Master, how could you be so heartless?
After all that I have done for you,
I wore the wedding gown you gave me
and got married on the same day.
I thought I would take her place
in your heart.
But you'd rather die and be with her.
What's the point of me staying alive?
Kai-hin, I hope to see you in the next life.
I won't let anyone keep us apart again.
How did our lives turn out like this?
(Hin)
Is it everything our own doing?
The doctor said Angie turned out like this
because she's too fixated on
our relationship.
She refused to give up even after
our divorce.
She used everything in her power
to make things happen.
When she came across the Chow mansion
and heard about the story of
Master Chow and Miss Koo
she projected her own experience
into their story.
Perhaps like the child bride in the story,
she was too anxious to win over
or to possess Master Chow,
even the kindest person
can become a terrifying lover.